AAYUSHI SINGH

A-1 Shanti Kunj, Om Gardens, Near Archana Vihar, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh 495001

T: +91 9039262124

E: aayushi.riyasingh001@gmail.com



Summary

I'm a web developer and have developed websites for my internships in various startups wherein I worked as a front end as well as a backend developer. There, I had worked on the development of modules of various services provided by the firm in Angular JS. I have been laying my hands on PHP framework Laravel from last 3 months and increasing my skillset. I'm a confident enthusiast who keeps trying and learning new stuffs.

Experience

Intern as Front End Developer, SelfIntern

Bilaspur — Dec,2015 - Feb,2016

Accomplishments

- Worked in AngularJS for Front end.
- Developed an effective UI keeping customers' ease as priority.
- Worked under supervision of a professional.

Intern as Full Stack Web Developer, Cumbre Technology

Work from home — June,2016 - Aug,2016

Accomplishments

- Worked in Laravel framework.
- Developed an effective UI keeping customers' ease as priority.
- Developed a discussion forum where users can ask, like, comment and answer other's questions.
- Created an admin panel.

Projects

Mini Project, E-Commerce Web Application

Feb 2016 - April 2016

Accomplishments

- Developed a user friendly UI.
- Front end was developed in AngularJS.
- Worked in Bootstrap to make the design responsive.
- Deviced the database schemas in MySQL.
- Back end was developed in PHP.

Self taken Project, Embedded System

Sep 2015 - Oct 2015

Accomplishments

- Build a visitor's counter to count the no. of entries and exits..
- Explored about embedded systems.
- Worked with sensors, seven segment, IC 8085.

Education

Guru Ghasidas Central University 9.2 (Till III Semester)

B.Tech, Information Technology — 2018

Sidhhi Vinayaka Higher Secondary School 85.8%

XII, CG Board — 2013

St. Francis Sr. Secondary School 9.8 CGPA

X, CBSE — 2011

Skills

- Programming Languages: C, C++, PHP(Laravel)
- Web Technologies: HTML5, CSS3 (Bootstrap), JavaScript (AngularJS).
- Software tools: Photoshop, Illustrator, Sublime Text
- Database: MySQL
- Operating Systems: Windows 7, Windows 8.

Extracurriculars

- Member in Cultural Events organizing team of college techfest EQUILIBRIO-2016
- Editorial Board member of college's magazine UDAAN 2015.

Trainings

- Embedded Systems ProLoT Pvt Ltd 2015.
- SEO Workshop by Neuromancers at NIT Raipur 2016.